export const quiz = {
  topic: 'Javascript',
  level: 'Beginner',
  totalQuestions: 4,
  perQuestionScore: 5,
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'What does "merci" mean in English?',
      choices: ['Yes', 'No', 'Thank you', 'Goodbye'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Thank you',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of the following words means "car" in French?',
      choices: ['Voiture', 'Maison', 'Chien', 'Chat'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Voiture',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which pronoun replaces "le livre" (the book) in French?',
      choices: ['Elle', 'Lui', 'La', 'Il'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Il',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the traditional French breakfast pastry often enjoyed with coffee?',
      choices: ['Baguette', 'Croissant', 'Pain au chocolat', 'Crêpe'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Croissant',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the French word for "summer"?',
      choices: ['Printemps', 'Hiver', 'Automne', 'Été'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Été',
    },
    {
      question: 'What does the expression "avoir le cafard" mean in English?',
      choices: ["To have butterflies in one's stomach", 'To have the blues', "To have a frog in one's throat", "To have ants in one's pants"],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'To have the blues',
    },
    {
      question: 'Who wrote the French classic "Le Petit Prince"?',
      choices: ['Victor Hugo', 'Albert Camus', 'Antoine de Saint-Exupéry', 'Marcel Proust'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Antoine de Saint-Exupéry',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which verb tense is used to express actions that were ongoing in the past in French?',
      choices: ['Passé composé', 'Imparfait', 'Futur simple', 'Plus-que-parfait'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Imparfait',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which historical event inspired the French national anthem, "La Marseillaise"?',
      choices: ['The French Revolution', "The Hundred Years' War", 'The Norman Conquest', 'The Renaissance'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'The French Revolution',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the English title of the French film "Amélie"?',
      choices: ['Love Actually', 'The Intouchables', 'Amélie', 'A Very Long Engagement'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Amélie',
    },
  ],
}